marketingforsuccess.com 2017-08-26

# Privacy Policy

**MarketingForSuccess.com Online Privacy Policy**

MarketingForSuccess.com is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.

**Basic Confidentiality Policy**

It is MarketingForSuccess.com policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information, such as to register or to customize an application.

If you also indicate that you would like to receive information about other MarketingForSuccess.com products and services, your personal information may be added to an appropriate MarketingForSuccess.com mailing list. If at any time you change your mind and would like to add or remove your name from a MarketingForSuccess.com mailing list, or correct your personal information, please contact us with the link provided for you with in each email.

**No Release of Information to Third Parties**

Personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information, or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.

**No Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information**

Our computer is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our sites. This information is used only for internal purposes by MarketingForSuccess.com technical support staff.
